ufobux.com 2013-01-05

# Privacy Notice : Designer Handbags,Wallets and Shoes Replica, Discount Louis Vuitton,Gucci,Chanel,Hermes Handbag

Our website is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services. We want to provide a safe and secure environment. This privacy policy is intended to assist you in understanding what information we gather when you visit the Site, how we use that information, and the safeguards we have in place to protect the information. This privacy policy only applies to information we collect at the Site.

 **The information we collect:**

 **Personal Information**

For purposes of this privacy policy, "personal information" means any information by which someone can be personally identified, including name, address, telephone number, email address, billing and account information, credit or debit card information, and other information incidental to providing goods or services. We collect personal information from you only when you voluntarily provide us with this information, such as when registering your account on the Site and placing an order through the Site.

 **Browsing Information: Cookies**

When you visit the Site, our web servers may automatically recognize certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your domain name, access provider, IP address, and browser language. The Site also uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. The information collected from cookies allows us to provide better customer service to you and improve features of our Site in a variety of ways, including by determining whether you have visited the Site in the past and which pages of our Site you have visited. We also may use cookies and/or a technology known as clear gifs to help us confirm your receipt of and response to our emails and to provide you a more personalized experience. Please note that certain pages of the Site may not function properly if cookies are turned off. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information about how to turn cookies on and off your browser.

 **Purchasing products or services**

If you purchase products you should register with us. It requires you to provide your personal information so that we can establish an account. This includes your name and contact information, or in the case of businesses, information about the company, department or association making the purchase or setting up the account. This information will help us process and manage your account.

 **How we use your information?**

We use personal information collected on the Site for the following purposes:

? to understand your needs and preferences;

? to develop, market, sell or provide products and services;

? to conduct surveys, research and evaluations;

? to manage and develop our business and operations, administer accounts, and collect and process payments;

? to detect and protect us and other third parties against negligence, fraud, theft and other illegal activities;

? as permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements, process or provisions.

 **Information sharing**

We may share your information with selected third parties who provide services to us, including to process payments, provide electronic online investor information, monitor Site activity, serve Site content, help to maintain our customer database, administer emails, surveys, or contests and administer and maintain employment application information.

 **Security**

We use certain security measures to protect the personal information you submit to the Site. For example, we use firewall technology, password controls, and other technological and procedural safeguards in maintaining the Site. Although we have implemented the above security measures for this Site, you should be aware that 100% security is not possible.

 **Managing Your Personal Information**

To allow us to serve you better we encourage you to regularly review and update your personal information.

You may obtain upon request a summary of the personal information on record with us. You also may request that we correct any such personal information about you, remove such information from its marketing databases, or dispose of any or all personal information about you.

To make any request described above, or if you have any questions about this privacy policy, send an email to eluxurybox@gmail.com .

When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact email address, name, mailing address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.

Please email to eluxurybox@gmail.com if you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement.

 **Changes to this privacy statement**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Any changes to our Privacy Statement will be highlighted in this area from time to time.
